Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Circulation Files 1940-1987 MS 3009-RG 50
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. International Distribution Files, 1945-1967; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  - Duarte: Agencia Selecciones (Colombia), 1949-1950, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 26)
  - Duarte: Agencia Selecciones (Colombia) [Restricted], 1952-1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Eason & Son, Ltd. Dublin, Ireland, 1949, 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Enterprise Khmere de Librairie, Phnon-Penh, Cambodia [Restricted], 1963 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Farajalla Press Agency Egypt [Restricted], 1956 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Farajalla Press Agency/Farajalla Travel Bureau, Lebanon, 1946, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 27)
  - Farajalla Press Agency/Farajalla Travel Bureau, Lebanon [Restricted], 1946 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Fardal, Rudolf Copenhagen, Denmark, 1948, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 28)
  - Fardal, Rudolf Copenhagen, Denmark [Restricted], 1948 (Offsite-box R86)
  - G.E. Willock - Georgetown, British Guiana, 1961 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 29)
  - Hanthawaddy Press Burma, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 30)
  - Hollywood Magazines - British Honduras, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 31)
  - Indira Bookstore Djarkarta, Indoneasia, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 32)
  - Indira Bookstore Djarkarta, Indoneasia [Restricted], 1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Ines Viuda de Pizarro - Santiago, Chile, 1952, 1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 33)
  - Ines Viuda de Pizarro - Santiago, Chile [Restricted], 1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - International Book & News Agency - Athens, Greece, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 34)
  - International Book & News Agency - Athens, Greece [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - International News Co. - England, 1947, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 35)
  - International News Co. - England [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - International Publicity League - Korea (Song), 1948, 1950, 1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 36)
  - International Publicity League - Korea (Song) [Restricted], 1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Iseli, Theo M. -British West Africa [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Japan Central Exchange, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 37)
  - John Martin, Pan-American Distributors, Port-of-Spain, Trinidad [Restricted], 1956 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Jose Garcia Baylleres, Antioquia, Colombia 1966 [Restricted] (Offsite-box R86)
  - Kappel, Paul J - Willemstad Cucao, 1951, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 38)
  - Kappel, Paul J - Willemstad Cucao [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Kelly & Walsh, Ltd. - Singapore, 1946 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 39)
  - Kingstons Ltd. Bulawayo Rhodesia [Restricted], 1955 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Kinki Kokoku K. Kaisha - Osaka, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 40)
  - Kiosk, A.G. Berne, Switzerland [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Kitao - Japan, 1949-1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 41)
  - Kitao - Japan [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Kolff, G. & Co. Batavia, Indonesia, 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 42)
  - Kraus, Messageries Paul - Luxembourg, 1948, 1963 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 43)
  - Kraus, Messageries Paul Luxembourg [Restricted], 1963 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Kyobunkwan - Tokyo, Japan, 1949-1950, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 44)
  - Kyobunkwan - Tokyo, Japan [Restricted], 1945, 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Lello & Co. Angola [Restricted], 1956 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Libraine Kauffmann - Athens, Greece, 1965 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 45)
  - Libraine Kauffmann - Athens, Greece [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Librairie Belge (Maison Desclee) - Leopoldville, Belgian Congo, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 46)
  - Librecia Nacional Limitada Barranquilla, Colombia 1966 [Restricted] (Offsite-box R86)
  - Libreria Iris - Colombia [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Libreria Iris - Colombia [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Libreria J. Villegas - Madrid, Spain, 1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 47)
  - Libros y Revistas, S.A. - Mexico, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 48)
  - Libros y Revistas, S.A. - Mexico [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Luri, Ediciones - Tangier, Morocco, 1948 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 49)
  - Macadam, H.M. Montevideo, Uruguay, 1948, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 50)
  - Marco, Angelo & Giovanni (A. & G.), Societe Italy, 1950, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 51)
  - Marco, Angelo & Giovanni (A. & G.), Societe Italy [Restricted]=, 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Mazarakis, Librarie - Istanbul, Turkey, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 52)
  - Melo, Juan G. Venezuela, 1953, 1956 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 53)
  - Melo, Juan G. Venezuela [Restricted], 1956 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Messageries Francaises de la Presse - Paris, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 54)
  - Meulenhoff & Co., 1951, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 55)
  - Meulenhoff & Co. [Restricted], 1947-1948 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Morawa & Co. Vienna 1, Austria, 1949, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 56)
  - Moseley's Ltd. Nassau, Bahamas, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 57)
  - Moseley's Ltd. Nassau, Bahamas [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Muller & Phipps – Phillipines [Restricted], 1962-1963 (Offsite-box R86)
  - News Brothers Ltd. Cork, Ireland [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Newspaper Enterprise Ltd. - Hongkong, 1950 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 58)
  - Newspaper Enterprise Ltd. - Hongkong [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Norman, I.P. - Independent News Co. - Havana, Cuba, 1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 59)
  - Orbis Newspaper Dept - Prague, Czechoslovakia [Restricted], 1946,1948 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Panperu, S.A. Lima, Peru [Restricted], 1957 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Pacific Book & Supply Corp, 1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 60)
  - Pacific News - Honolulu, Hawaii, 1945, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 61)
  - Pacific News - Honolulu, Hawaii [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Pales Press Co. Ltd. - Tel Aviv, Palestine, 1946 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 62)
  - Pena, Alberto Araoz - Lima, Peru, 1947-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 63)
  - Pena, Alberto Araoz - Lima, Peru [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Pereira, A. Goncalves - Lisbon, Portugal, 1951, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 64)
  - Pereira, A. Goncalves - Lisbon, Portugal [Restricted], 1952 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Perez, Benigno y Hermano (Hno), - Havana, Cuba, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 65)
  - Perez, Benigno y Hermano (Hno), - Havana, Cuba [Restricted], 1952-1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Philippine Education Co., Inc. Manila, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 66)
  - Philippine Education Co., Inc. Manila [Restricted], 1953-1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Post Publishing Company (A. MacDonald), 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 67)
  - Press Agencias Sociedad Anonima Venezuela, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 68)
  - Press Agencias Sociedad Anonima Venezuela [Restricted], 1952-1954, 1966 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Publishers Distributing Corp. Ltd. - Johannesburg, 1947-1951, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 69)
  - Publishers Distributing Corp. Ltd. - Johannesburg [Restricted], 1947-1948, 1951 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Restrepo Armenia, Sr. Camilo - Distribuidora Colombiana, Colombia, 1950, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 70)
  - Riva Hermanos, De la - Guatemala, Central America (C.A.), 1952, 1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 71)
  - Riva Hermanos, De la - Guatemala, Central America (C.A.) [Restricted], 1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Roberts, T.A.L. Barbados, British West Indies (B.W.I.), 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 72)
  - Robertson, George, A. St. Vincent, British West Indies (B.W.I.), 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 73)
  - Ryukyus Newspaper Agency - Okinawa (Ikemiyagi), 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 74)
  - Ryukyus Newspaper Agency - Okinawa (Ikemiyagi) [Restricted], 1952 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Saenz, Carlos V. - Agente de Publicaciones, Costa Rica, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 75)
  - Saenz, Carlos V. - Agente de Publicaciones, Costa Rica [Restricted], 1952-1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Samuhos, Anastas -French-American Bookstore, Istanbul, Turkey, 1952-1956 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 76)
  - Samuhos, Anastas -French-American Bookstore, Istanbul, Turkey [Restricted], 1956 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Sasangge Monthly- Mr. Chang Chun-Ha, Korea [Restricted], 1959 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Sauerberg, F.W. - Hamburg, Germany, 1948 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 77)
  - Schmidt, Paul – Agence de Journaux - Basel, Switzerland [Restricted], 1947 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Seymour Press Limited London, England [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Shoucair & Co., F.S., 1946, 1949 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 78)
  - Singbal - Portuguesa India (Goa) [Restricted], 1957 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Singh Associates, Port-of-Spain, Trinidad, 1966 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 79)
  - Singh Associates, Port-of-Spain, Trinidad [Restricted], 1967 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Slavik, Peter B. - Interpass - Sofia, Bulgaria, 1946 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 80)
  - Sociedad General Espanola de Libreria, 1950 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 81)
  - Societe Franco-Asiatique - Paris, 1950 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 82)
  - Soto, Percy - Libreria Panamericana - Tegucigalpa, Honduras, 1952 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 83)
  - Spanos, D. - LDA, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 84)
  - Steimaktsky's Middle East Agency - Tel Aviv, Israel, 1948-1952, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 85)
  - Steiner & Schoening - El Salvador, Central America, 1948, 1951-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 86)
  - Steiner & Schoening - El Salvador, Central America [Restricted], 1948, 1952, 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Stumpf, Gerard - Libreria Internacional - Santiago, Chile, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 87)
  - Stumpf, Gerard - Libreria Internacional - Santiago, Chile [Restricted], 1967 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Transports Presse - Paris, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 88)
  - Trinidad Mirror Newspapers Limited - Time and Life Trinidad [Restricted], 1963 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Tripple "W" & Novelty Store - Monrovia, Liberia, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 89)
  - Tuttle Company, Charles E. - Tokyo, Japan (Civilian) [Restricted], 1956 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Ulistein - Berlin, Germany, 1952, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 90)
  - Ulistein - Berlin, Germany [Restricted], 1949 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Union Comercial del Caribe, Barranquilla, Colombia, 1947, 1951, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 91)
  - U.S. Trading Corp., Ohio, 1949-1951 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 92)
  - Valdes, Eusebio, Distribuidors Selecciones, 1949-1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 93)
  - Valdes, Eusebio, Distribuidors Selecciones [Restricted], 1952-1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Venegas, Leopolde - St. Thomas, Virgin Islands, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 94)
  - Venegas, Leopolde - St. Thomas, Virgin Islands [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Wade, E.M. - Lago Oil & Transport Co. - Aruba, Netherlands West Indies, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 95)
  - Wade, E.M. - Lago Oil & Transport Co. - Aruba, Netherlands West Indies [Restricted], 1953 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Wennergren-Williams - Stockholm, Sweden, 1947, 1949 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 96)
  - Wennergren-Williams - Stockholm, Sweden [Restricted], 1947, 1948 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Western Press Ltd., 1951, 1955 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 97)
  - Western Press Ltd. [Restricted], 1955 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Willis H. Bird Inc. Bangkok, Thailand, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 98)
  - Willis H. Bird Inc. Bangkok, Thailand [Restricted], 1954 (Offsite-box R86)
  - Yugoslovenka Knjige - Belgrade, 1951, 1953 (Offsite-box 4084, Folder 99)
- Series III. Magazine Development Files, 1971-1973; 1.25 Linear feet 1 in record carton and 2 flat folders
  The Magazine Development Files include records from Irene Sullivan and Ann Brown of Corporate Circulation and document Corporate Circulation's collaboration with the Magazine Development Group. Corporate Circulation handled the market testing of and the enrollment of charter subscribers to magazines still in development. Camera Month initially tried to publish in the spring of 1973, but sent letters to the charter subscribers announcing a delay.
  Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed.
  - General, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 2)
  - Tests, 1972 January-February (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 3)
  - Camera Month: General, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 4-5)
  - Camera Month: Acknowledgement mailing, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 6)
  - Camera Month: Correspondence: Charter subscribers, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 7-9)
  - Camera Month: Correspondence: Delay, 1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 10)
  - Camera Month: Correspondence: Institution subscribers, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 11-12)
  - Camera Month: Donors: General, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 13)
  - Camera Month: Donors: Non-subscription, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 14-15)
  - Camera Month: Donors: Subscription, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 16-17)
  - Camera Month: Deletes from launch mail, 1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 18)
  - Camera Month: Francis-Lefman brochure, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 19)
  - Camera Month: Invoices, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 20)
  - Camera Month: Launch projections, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 21)
  - Camera Month: List proposals, 1973 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 22)
  - Camera Month: Retest: lists, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 23)
  - Camera Month: Retest: Mailing, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 24)
  - Camera Month: Retest: Orders, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 25)
  - Camera Month: Retest: Returns, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 26)
  - Camera Month and View: Final report, 1972 (Offsite-box 4182, Folder 9)
  - Money and Well: Test, 1971 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 27)
  - View: General, 1973 (Offsite-box 4182, Folder 10)
  - View and Well: Acknowledgement mailing, 1972 (Offsite-box 4277, Folder 28)